# **Summary of Qualifications**

Self-motivated fully certified technology specialist with extensive educational and professional experience in the fields of Information Technology, security, software design and development, hardware maintenance and repair, and troubleshooting. Experienced small business owner offering services such as consultation, computer repair, virus removal, home installations and configurations.

#### **Technical Skills**

- Software: MS Office, Adobe Suite, Various Java/C++ Compilers, Visual Studio, Five9, HediSQL, MySQL
- Operating Systems: DOS, Windows XP-8.1, Mac OS X, Android, Linux
- Networking Technology & Computer Imaging: Firewalls, VPN, Virtualization, Server Administration, Active Directory, Remote Desktop, Group Policies, VB Scripting, Packet Tracing, MS Deployment Tools, VoIP, Subnetting, TCP/IPv4&v6, DNS, DHCP
- Hardware: Desktops, Laptops, Netbooks, MacBook, Android, iPhone, BlackBerry
- Scripting/Programming Languages: HTML5, CSS3, XML, Bootstrap, JavaScript, JQUERY, AJAX, JSON, PHP, ASP.NET, Java, C++, bash, PowerShell, VB, SQL

### **Education**

# **Great Bay Community College**

January 2012 - Current

- Associates Degree in Computer Technology
- Graduated Cum Laude and top of CT
- 2015 New Century Scholar Representing the state of New Hampshire
- Member of Phi Theta Kappa
- Nominated for Kappa Beta Delta
- All-USA Community College Academic Team

#### Certifications

- → Dell Network Certified

  → Dell Notebook Certified

  → WorkPoort \*\*\*\*
- WorkReadyNH Certificate 2014
   JavaScript Certified
- National Career Readiness Certificate – Gold Level 2014
- Dell Printer Certified

  - JQuery Certified
  - Certified Tutor Lv.1

#### September 2014 - Current

- > Five9 Certified (VoIP)
- CSS Certified
- > HTML Certified
- AJAX Certified

# **Professional Experience**

# **Southern New Hampshire University**

April 2015 - Current

## **Customer Liaison Lv.1**

- Provide accurate information to students, staff, and faculty whom require technical assistance
- Find new solutions to ever changing demands
- Research problems, work with customers, and find their optimal solution
- Provide impromptu solutions to customers via phone, email, and chat services
- Provide instructions and demonstrations to students, instructors, and fellow staff members
- Communicate effectively with coworkers to obtain and share knowledge of new and ongoing issues

## **EL-ectronics.com PC Services & Repair**

June 2005 - Current

## Owner, Technology Support Specialist, web designer

- Consult with customers, find their needs, and offer various solutions
- Provide reliable and timely computer repairs , upgrades, and installations
- Research problems, work with customers, and find their optimal solution
- Install, configure, and customize home networks and home theater systems
- Consult, research, and build custom computers for customers

## **Alexander Technology Group**

### Southern New Hampshire University

September 2014 - November 2014

### **ITS Field Services (Temporary Position)**

- o Imaged computers and configured software for internal deployment
- o Identified and resolved computer related issues
- o Developed software which cut software configuration times in half

# **Durgin Pines Assisted Living Facility**

January 2013 - July 2014

### Dishwasher

Maintained clean dishes and area in a fast-paced work environment

# <u>Leddy Group</u> September 2014 – Current

## Various temporary assignments

Kittery Trading Post

July 2013 – January 2014

#### **Warehouse Associate**

 Accurately located products in warehouse or sales floor and prepared it for delivery to online buyers

## **Geskus Photography**

August 2012 – November 2012

## **Student Photographer**

Positioned and photographed students K-12 for their school photos

## Regal Cinemas December 2012 – July 2013

Usher

Provided friendly service in a fast-paced environment

## **Great Bay Community College**

May 2012 - August 2012

#### **Administrative Assistant**

- Professionally handled incoming and outgoing calls to potential students
- General office duties (copy, print, organize)
- Assisted students in operating the GBCC computer system

#### BJ's Wholesale Club

May 2011 - May 2012

#### **General Associate**

- Cashier Performed accurate and timely transactions
- Stock clerk Insured inventory was stocked and placed properly

## GameStop July 2010 – January 2011

#### **Lead Game Advisor**

- Opened/Closed the store
- > Trained new employees
- Performed daily deposits
- Monitored inventory/Placed orders